Jamie Henry

jamiehenry802@gmail.com

(321) 576-5440

linkedin.com/in/jamie-henry-8ba765154

https://jayhenry07.github.io/

Summary

I am a competitive and versatile Software Developer with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering from the University of Central Florida. I have a passion for computers, technology, video games and I enjoy problem solving and analyzing algorithms. I have been writing code for over a decade and have multiple years of experience working on both mobile and web Full-Stack applications.

Experience



Mobile Application Developer

BladeDocs®

Mar 2023 - Present (1 year)

Full Stack Developer

PwC

Aug 2022 - Present (1 year 7 months)

SIGNILSTORM Full Stack Developer

SkillStorm

May 2022 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Education



University of Central Florida

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering Aug 2019 - May 2022



Lake-Sumter State College

Associate's degree, General Studies Aug 2017 - May 2019

Licenses & Certifications



- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp
- Java Foundations Certified Junior Associate Certification Oracle

- (A) Back End Development and APIs freeCodeCamp
- (A) Scientific Computing with Python freeCodeCamp

Skills

Full-Stack Development • Cloud Firestore • Firebase • React Native • TypeScript • REST APIs • Spring Framework • React.js • AngularJS • Spring Boot

Honors & Awards



Mathematics Award - Lake-Sumter State College

Apr 2019

For academic excellence and achievement in mathematics.